NADER AWADALA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



- **1** +359 87 675 3994
- naderawadala@gmail.com
- Check out my website
- Check out my Github
- in Add me on LinkedIn

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript
- React.js, Redux.js
- OOP, SOLID principles
- C#
- Java
- .NET Core, .NET Framework
- Elixir
- MSSQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL
- · Git, Docker, Jira

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

"St. Cyril and St. Methodius" University of Veliko Tarnovo

2018 - 2022

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Secondary School "Emiliyan Stanev" 2013-2018

PROFILE

I am a young and eager software engineer who has experience in building solutions to complex problems within the business world. Innovation excites me and I always look for ways in which I can contribute and bring new things to the table.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

pressrelations

Feb 2022 - Mar 2023

- Developing responsive, cross-browser, and user-friendly web applications and collaborating with UX/Design department.
- Working on innovative software applications that solve diverse and complex challenges in accordance to design guidelines and coding standards and conventions.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

clouway

Jul 2021 - Feb 2022

- Closely working with a small team in an office environment and collaborating to develop software related to ERP systems.
- Learning how to work with Git and Docker as well as being introduced and accustomed to the Agile/SCRUM methodology.

FREELANCER

Jan 2021 - Jul 2021

- Working part-time for local small businesses and creating and helping maintain websites to display their products.
- Various freelance work on UpWork